[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fergie"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Now, what have I done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "I love Fergie, it's a great name.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Did you really do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sarah Ferguson Foundation"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Did she really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "She came to Wall Street and she sang for the Sarah Ferguson Foundation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What was Sarah like before the royal experience began?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, I actually was thinking before I came on this show that actually Sarah is the same sitting here as she was then, she just made a few road changes and changed course a few times.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "That's when you first met him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "And do you remember that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Yes, very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "``", "VBG", "''", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "When you first started actually dating him, did you have any comprehension of what you were getting yourself into?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, Piers, I think the word \"dating\" is kind of interesting because when you go -- when you date a prince back in those long years ago, 26 years ago, it's not -- you can't actually go on a date.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "As fast as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "As fast as that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "What was that moment like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Let me go back in time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Do you think he knew what you were going to be immersed in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "He had a much better idea than I did, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Do you think they've learned from what they saw you go through, how to play negative media perhaps a little better than you were able to because they saw the way to do it well and the way maybe not to do it so well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, Piers, you know what's so great is they have got a great role model of mistakes to follow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Oh, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I think it's more of a -- it's a cultural thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ":", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "But that experience, when it turned, what was that like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, I think that I believed the good press for the two years before then -- so, I was believing my own press, which is the most dangerous thing you can do, isn't it, because now I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrew"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "When there was a point of no return, did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "The thing about Andrew is that really our love is so strong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "I mean, is it completely unthinkable that one day the two of you could actually get back together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, I think that -- as I said, we're a very modern fairy tale.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "What are your biggest regrets, as the marriage fell apart and the press dived in, and all these exposes about you and your life, what for you personally were the things you most regret now doing in that period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Every minute of my day, I have to work on regret now, Piers, every day, because I regret divorcing and I regret that I wasn't more aware.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Do you feel ashamed of your behavior in that period?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Phil", "Martha Beck"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "RB", ":", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Or do you feel it was kind of a consequence of all the attacks on you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I think looking back -- of course, with having worked with Dr. Phil and Suze Orman and Martha Beck and Oprah, looking back -- goodness, with the awareness I have now, yes, I feel so totally ashamed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "VBG", ",", "``", "UH", ",", "DT", ",", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 344, "question": "When you saw that front page, what went through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, I remember seeing it and just going, \"Oh, no, Sarah.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "And that's when Carolyn, my best friend in the world -- do you remember Carolyn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carolyn", "Carolyn?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "How did Andrew react when he saw that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, like he always reacts when anything is written or anything is said about me or the girls, complete solidarity to his family.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrew"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Of all the royals over the years, who have been the most supportive to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, I think like anybody who divorces a family member, it's -- you know, you mustn't ever expect to be invited.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Thailand"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "How did you feel that day watching it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Well, Piers, I was in Thailand at a place called Kamilayah (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "So it's pretty good here, isn't' it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "POS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Your girls were great that day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "That charity is very dear to your heart, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Yes, very dear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "What was she like, Diana?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, before she got married, I called her Dutch, because she was born for it, you know, born to be a princess.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Do you remember her wit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "She was hilarious.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "What was that about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Well, we don't really know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Italy"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Where were you when you heard that she died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I was in Italy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How would she have felt on the royal wedding day, do you think, watching her boy, William going down the aisle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "ERGUSON: Honestly, total pride, total pride.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Be honest here, knowing her well, what do you think she would have made of Kate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I think they -- I don't know except they would have been the best friends.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Pretty impressive Kate, isn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I take my hat off to her.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Do you worry about the pressure that you know she's going to be facing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I think she's able to cope with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "I think so, don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Totally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny", "Johnny"]}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "When you realized that -- what was happening to the people in there and you realized how close you came to being one of them, what was going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I think my friend who helped me with the charity, Johnny -- I think Johnny has never really got over it, because he just couldn't believe it, because that was his world, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "When William and Kate go to Hollywood, it's going to be pretty crazy, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "I think it's going to be amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William and Kate"], "LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "You didn't remember it very often, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Would you like to find a new Mr. Right in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "I always say when you've had the best, forget the rest, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110609pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "We can do CNN dateline?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"]}}]